大家好
我是小舞
今天我和大家一同观赏的是
2015年苏迪曼杯决赛
第三盘男子单打的较量
由中国队的林丹对阵日本队的上田拓马
三比六单块推拉开远网
控制上前推
转身劈杀斜线单
潇洒卸力挡网得分
五比六单发
后场加力抽直线推转身
往前停顿
控转身
滑板斜线平高压
转身往前分对角
辣妹单品高低出上田
摆脱击杀对手的伤
He made the mistake of playing ldan with time in his forehand
That clear is so well
Disguised
八比九
单停顿推转身往前分对角平高压转身单登必杀
斜线得分
Three four hand oppression
头顶杀斜线上前侧身突击
单头顶直线进攻成功斜线
上田高质量回扣得分
Great shop
The only weight playing in dan is to be pressure
I'm just waiting for that to happen in dan here one
Because we haven't seen a really fast pace game
单抽奖取得进攻机会
14比13上前斜线过渡
单头顶插一插上
沿斜线摆脱
单头顶直线突击上旋发起力压三半蹲
把球顶回后场
重伤弟弟旁边大红
But where his feet are inside that double service line
二十六三
单下压控网上田快推拉开
What can use it
How on earth did he play that get out of trouble
16比13
上田接杀分
斜线杀
中路追身
往前低压单秀出神龙摆尾
No indication of his confidence
14比16
上田发后长单下压推转身
再推转身
滑板吊球
往前分斜线
He simply not able to read
Which shot is coming to pull my way up
18比14
双方出场较量
单推转身停顿推球
单推转身
抓不住
劈杀斜线得分
He's gonna make a move
We weren't kidding wor
第14单推转身14
上田杀上网单秀出超强防守
头顶杀对手攻
To hakisn't it
The ability to win points of ro
这是20比14上填空网
连续进攻得分
差不多可以15比23点杀直线往前分球
平高压转身接杀斜线摆脱控转身上前反拍过渡
直接game
起跳杀球得分
三比二
上田劈杀斜线单挡网
往前分斜线
正手扶梯一拍
上田高质量搓球得分
Absolutely right back of the cord
And then decided to play it
Look at this
And you don't have to play that sharp in your own band
五比四
双方联网控制三头顶杀斜线上
填高质量防守得分
And stretch
How did he generate place to fix the bone
感觉本身发波主正手直线进攻
火五比六
单直接头顶直接突击得分
七比五
暂停顿放网
侧身
Look at this
Look at it
单推转身
单击沙台
后场再推转身
I remember the left hand of nability
As well
Please watching this match
I think about what do you pressure
You know
How do you tell you
Can't no
You can't tell
And that's the problem
Yeah
This one cross courts
it's双方斗网
单起跳杀中路追身得分
Don't be control afterwards
单推头顶
Just played against the better player
头顶加一开
双方斗网
双方抽打漂亮
上填空
转身往前扑压
上田高质量吊球得分
怎么没叫我
And down dive can't do anything about that
哈哈12比八
上田头顶杀斜线单防守反击
上田高质量防守得分
九比12上田直接劈杀斜线得分
15比十单反拍过渡上田停顿推杆
但正手抽压直线被判界外
Oh go on
Have a challenge
Yes
Good man
A little bit late perhaps that challenge
Yeah
But anyway signing for nindeed
It de
That's quite off the player
You can see that
往前斜线
单击杀反对角
FOFENSE单推转身
双方出场较量
上田杀上网单极限一跃过
但上田不求出界
And punched the camera man in the face at the same time
Very good ng out
And the question on it was wrong
12比19
单抓过度
头顶直线突击得分
13比20
暂停顿
最转身让开吧
最终单劈杀斜线拿下本场比赛胜利
帮助中国队锁定苏迪曼杯决赛胜利
For attempts time
They will lift the prestigious trophy
And can claim the status of world
Mixing champions
As sixth consecutive title
How fitting that it is the two time olympic champion lynd
When when need a third hatch
Twenty one fifteen
Twenty one thirteen
温暖提示
我们邀请现场所有哥们来
我们一同见证中国的在这个世界
Countries support staff
Well it is a trophy that they have made their own
This was their eleven final
And a tenth sumon cup title
And this is
How it was one